Zeerak Waseem and Dirk Hovy. 2016. Hateful symbols
or hateful people? predictive features for hate
speech detection on twitter. In Proceedings of the
NAACL Student ResearchWorkshop. Association for
Computational Linguistics, San Diego, California,
pages 88–93.

研究的问题：
什么样的特征能够提升敏感词检测的性能


目标：
特征--性别 词汇 地理位置

方法：
分类器--逻辑回归


结果与结论：
基于字符n-grams方法表现得很好，除了性别以外的如词汇和地理位置特征并没有带来性能上的提升(可能是因为缺少覆盖)

存在的问题：

观点的不足与尚未解决的问题：
将来改善位置和性别分类来更新数据和实验




A tweet is offensive if it
1. uses a sexist or racial slur.
2. attacks a minority.
3. seeks to silence a minority.
4. criticizes a minority (without a well founded
argument).
5. promotes, but does not directly use, hate
speech or violent crime.
6. criticizes a minority and uses a straw man argument.
7. blatantly misrepresents truth or seeks to distort
views on a minority with unfounded
claims.
8. shows support of problematic hash tags. E.g.
“#BanIslam”, “#whoriental”, “#whitegenocide”
9. negatively stereotypes a minority.
10. defends xenophobia or sexism.
11. contains a screen name that is offensive, as
per the previous criteria, the tweet is ambiguous
(at best), and the tweet is on a topic that
satisfies any of the above criteria.